Lior Hajaj Junior Developer

♀ Qiryat Ono ⋈ lior11082@gmail.com 、 0525676332 ♠ https://github.com/LiorHajaj

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/lior-hajaj/

PROFILE

Computer science student in my 3rd year, and Junior Developer with a year of experience working in an administrative position as an assistant manager of technical support team, extremely motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally, excellent debugger and problem tracker, self-taught, fast learner and highly efficient with a strong desire to learn new technologies.

Graduating in Feb 2023.

EDUCATION

Ono Academic College, B.Sc. degree in Computer Science

2019 - present

Significant Courses: Intro to Computer Science, Data Structures and Algorithms, Software Programming with Java, Computer Architecture with C, Intro to Al.

PROJECTS

myBot, A WhatsApp bot which its purpose is to make mundane tasks easier, I've used whatsapp-web.js library and several technologies like API calls, web scraping and URL manipulation.

Portfolio Site, A portfolio website presenting my projects and knowledge. In this project I've used multiple technologies like React, NodeJS, Express, it contains a newsletter built using the Mailchimp API and its been deployed to Heroku.

Smart City, This project is about multithreading "SmartCity" which contains a roadway system that implements the Dijkstra algorithm while keeping track of vehicles, traffic lights and oncoming traffic, using Java and OOP principals..

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Assistant Manager Technical Support, Ono Academic College

10/2021 - present

- Create troubleshooting guides and solving technical problems.
- Assistant manager for the support team that consisted of 15 employees.
- Implementation of hybrid class systems, providing to group and individual instructions on proper and efficient use In the system for long distance learning.
- Providing technical support to internal organizational employees and academic staff.

IT Support, Simteam

02/2019 - 09/2020

- Responsible for operating Simboost software, real-time troubleshooting, debugging and upgrading suggestions for upgrading the system to improve working methods.
- Arrangement of technical equipment.

SKILLS

- Hands-on: Java, Python, Git, Postman, DOM & ¡Query, Deploying with Heroku & Github Pages, OOP principals.
- Client side: React, HTML5, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap.
- Server side: NodeJS, Express, Java Spring, MySQL, MongoDB.
- Operating Systems- Windows, basic knowledge in Linux/Unix, proficient with using terminal commands.

LANGUAGES

- · Hebrew- Native
- English Proficient

VOLUNTEERING

Ono Entrepreneurs, IT Support Technician & Club Member.

Our goal is to create an entrepreneurial home for students at the Ono Academic College, to bring quality content, to improve networking, to create an exclusive and closed community that will be the spearhead of the largest college in Israel.